(Sheldon:)Uh, first, music is dangerous.
The movie Footloose tried to
warn us, but we wouldn't listen.
(Sheldon:)Oh, wait.
♪ Everybody cut footloo... ♪
(Sheldon(singing):)Nope.
I'll pay $1,000 to watch you
cut footloose.
(Sheldon:)This is Penny.
(Sheldon:)She is your friend.
(Sheldon:)If she offers you food,
it's safe to take it.
(Sheldon:)You probably
paid for it, anyway.
(Bernadette:)So, you're really going out
with Dave again?
(Amy:)Why not?
(Amy:)He's actually a very nice guy.
(Bernadette:)But he spent an entire date
(Bernadette:)talking about how much
he loves Sheldon.
(Amy:)That's nothing Sheldon
hasn't done before.
(Amy:)Dave's just a big
fan of his work.
(Amy:)Besides, he said he
wouldn't bring it up again.
(Bernadette:)Okay. So where's he taking you?
(Amy:)Oh, he's coming here.
I'm actually making dinner.
(Bernadette:)Oh. That's a big step.
(Amy:)It is?
(Bernadette:)Yeah. You're inviting him
into your home.
(Bernadette:)It's intimate.
(Bernadette:)It's where your underpants live.